{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{60} \\div \\dfrac{55}{62}\\)",
      "answer": "217/1650",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1650]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{53}{3}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "2809/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 9]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{24}{73} + \\dfrac{13}{29}\\)",
      "answer": "1645/2117",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2117]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{88}{49} + \\dfrac{13}{24}\\)",
      "answer": "2749/1176",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1176]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-89}{40}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "7921/1600",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1600]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-21}{16} \\div \\dfrac{-11}{40}\\)",
      "answer": "105/22",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 22]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8 \\div 3.4\\)",
      "answer": "40/17",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 17]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-33}{10}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "1089/100",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 100]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{4}{53} \\div \\dfrac{27}{97}\\)",
      "answer": "388/1431",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1431]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(0.74 \\geq \\dfrac{17}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{31}{35} \\div 0\\)",
      "answer": "n/a",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": []
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{39}{49} \\leq -5.1\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(0.02\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-1/50",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 50]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.057 \\div \\dfrac{-50}{81}\\)",
      "answer": "-4617/50000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 50000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{13}{92} \\div 81\\)",
      "answer": "13/7452",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 7452]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{62}{83} - -0.042\\)",
      "answer": "32743/41500",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 41500]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(0.05 \\leq 16\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(9.4\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-47/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 5]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{81}{92} \\geq \\dfrac{89}{91}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.1 - 0.052\\)",
      "answer": "6/125",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 125]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{62}{17}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "3844/289",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 289]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(4 > \\dfrac{-17}{24}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{24}{41} \\div -70\\)",
      "answer": "-12/1435",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1435]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{26}{37} \\div \\dfrac{95}{91}\\)",
      "answer": "2366/3515",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 3515]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{17} \\div \\dfrac{-64}{87}\\)",
      "answer": "-261/1088",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1088]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 - \\dfrac{6}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "1/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 7]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{41}{46} \\geq -0.002\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-28}{93} \\div \\dfrac{2}{15}\\)",
      "answer": "-70/31",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 31]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-6}{13}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-216/2197",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2197]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3.3 \\div \\dfrac{80}{83}\\)",
      "answer": "2739/800",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 800]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(39 \\div \\dfrac{10}{29}\\)",
      "answer": "1131/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 10]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-21}{71} - \\dfrac{98}{43}\\)",
      "answer": "-7861/3053",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 3053]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{26}{33}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "17576/35937",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 35937]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-93}{49} \\div \\dfrac{66}{35}\\)",
      "answer": "-155/154",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 154]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-11}{10}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "121/100",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 100]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{37}{25} - \\dfrac{53}{56}\\)",
      "answer": "747/1400",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1400]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{8}{49} \\div 16\\)",
      "answer": "1/98",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 98]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-38}{31} \\geq 6.5\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{9}{44}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "81/1936",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1936]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{71}{88} \\div \\dfrac{49}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "355/4312",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 4312]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-6}{47} \\div 0.61\\)",
      "answer": "-600/2867",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2867]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{21}{23}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "441/529",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 529]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.6 + -0.19\\)",
      "answer": "-79/100",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 100]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-32}{17} - \\dfrac{5}{47}\\)",
      "answer": "-1589/799",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 799]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{44}{27} - \\dfrac{37}{32}\\)",
      "answer": "409/864",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 864]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{83}{11} \\div 8.7\\)",
      "answer": "830/957",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 957]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{2} \\div \\dfrac{29}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "22/29",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 29]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{77}{10} \\geq 0.94\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{29}{5} + 27\\)",
      "answer": "164/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{43}{82} - \\dfrac{26}{37}\\)",
      "answer": "-541/3034",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 3034]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-31}{15} \\div 1.8\\)",
      "answer": "-31/27",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 27]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(4.7 = \\dfrac{47}{58}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{92}{85} \\div \\dfrac{82}{57}\\)",
      "answer": "2622/3485",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 3485]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{22}{89} \\div \\dfrac{68}{59}\\)",
      "answer": "649/3026",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 3026]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-76 \\div \\dfrac{3}{32}\\)",
      "answer": "-2432/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 3]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{47}{37} \\div \\dfrac{-61}{85}\\)",
      "answer": "-3995/2257",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2257]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(56 \\div 0.067\\)",
      "answer": "56000/67",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 67]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{36}{7} \\div \\dfrac{13}{24}\\)",
      "answer": "864/91",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 91]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(45 - \\dfrac{44}{41}\\)",
      "answer": "1801/41",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 41]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{21}{22} \\div \\dfrac{14}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "9/44",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 44]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{85}{64} \\div \\dfrac{23}{33}\\)",
      "answer": "2805/1472",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1472]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(1\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-1",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.095 - \\dfrac{-64}{23}\\)",
      "answer": "12363/4600",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 4600]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.058 \\div \\dfrac{62}{15}\\)",
      "answer": "87/6200",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 6200]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{9}{16} \\div \\dfrac{7}{83}\\)",
      "answer": "747/112",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 112]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-1}{86} \\div \\dfrac{46}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "-7/3956",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 3956]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(-22\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "484",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{49}{40} > 0.034\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{59}{33} \\div \\dfrac{-11}{70}\\)",
      "answer": "-4130/363",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 363]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5 \\div 4\\)",
      "answer": "5/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 4]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-70}{43} \\div \\dfrac{-49}{16}\\)",
      "answer": "160/301",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 301]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{13}{7} + \\dfrac{29}{98}\\)",
      "answer": "211/98",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 98]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(0.25 \\geq \\dfrac{6}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{23}{32} \\div \\dfrac{-9}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "-115/288",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 288]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7.8 \\div 0.057\\)",
      "answer": "2600/19",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 19]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{7} \\div \\dfrac{23}{47}\\)",
      "answer": "235/161",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 161]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.024 \\div -0.034\\)",
      "answer": "-12/17",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 17]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-9.3 \\div 0.038\\)",
      "answer": "-4650/19",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 19]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{74}{27} \\div \\dfrac{6}{25}\\)",
      "answer": "925/81",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 81]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{3} + \\dfrac{45}{13}\\)",
      "answer": "148/39",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 39]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-8}{31} \\div \\dfrac{15}{22}\\)",
      "answer": "-176/465",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 465]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.37 - 7.9\\)",
      "answer": "-753/100",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 100]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{13}{10} \\div 0.091\\)",
      "answer": "100/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 7]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.013 \\div \\dfrac{65}{14}\\)",
      "answer": "-7/2500",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2500]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{44}{39} < \\dfrac{47}{39}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{39}{29} - \\dfrac{8}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-115/87",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 87]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{59} \\div \\dfrac{-15}{67}\\)",
      "answer": "-67/177",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 177]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{93}{89}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "804357/704969",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 704969]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(12 \\div \\dfrac{16}{75}\\)",
      "answer": "225/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 4]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-61}{49} \\div \\dfrac{33}{20}\\)",
      "answer": "-1220/1617",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1617]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(-0.091\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "91/1000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-6}{19}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "36/361",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 361]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(\\dfrac{66}{59}\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-66/59",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 59]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(55 + \\dfrac{1}{6}\\)",
      "answer": "331/6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 6]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{47}{23} + \\dfrac{6}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "467/161",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 161]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(0.72 > \\dfrac{29}{26}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(2.8 \\leq \\dfrac{12}{65}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{46}{31} \\div \\dfrac{-10}{83}\\)",
      "answer": "-1909/155",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 155]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{63}{55} \\div \\dfrac{-2}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-189/110",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 110]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(0.53\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-53/100",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 100]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{14}{9} < 87\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-13 + 2\\)",
      "answer": "-11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-2}{3} \\div 0.86\\)",
      "answer": "-100/129",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 129]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 \\div \\dfrac{1}{67}\\)",
      "answer": "67",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{15}{73} - 91\\)",
      "answer": "-6628/73",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 73]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(\\dfrac{36}{13}\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-36/13",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 13]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-11}{47}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-1331/103823",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 103823]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{71}{96}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "357911/884736",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 884736]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0.95\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "361/400",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 400]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{13} \\div \\dfrac{-14}{23}\\)",
      "answer": "-253/182",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 182]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7.8 \\div \\dfrac{22}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "273/110",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 110]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{2} \\geq \\dfrac{28}{25}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(-9.8 < 1.4\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{10} + \\dfrac{-80}{41}\\)",
      "answer": "-759/410",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 410]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(-87\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-658503",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{9}{40} = \\dfrac{85}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{83}{63} \\div 5\\)",
      "answer": "83/315",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 315]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{27}{23} + 6.7\\)",
      "answer": "1811/230",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 230]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-7}{86} + 0.26\\)",
      "answer": "192/1075",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1075]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{87}{71}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "658503/357911",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 357911]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-1}{3} < 12\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-1}{2} - 0.079\\)",
      "answer": "-579/1000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1000]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{81}{97} \\geq 98\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.066 \\div 9.3\\)",
      "answer": "11/1550",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1550]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4 + \\dfrac{30}{83}\\)",
      "answer": "362/83",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 83]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.001 \\div \\dfrac{7}{13}\\)",
      "answer": "13/7000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 7000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(82\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "6724",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-14}{23} \\div \\dfrac{-8}{31}\\)",
      "answer": "217/92",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 92]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-88}{3} \\div \\dfrac{81}{17}\\)",
      "answer": "-1496/243",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 243]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{28}{87} - \\dfrac{58}{69}\\)",
      "answer": "-346/667",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 667]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-6}{49}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "36/2401",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2401]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 + 15\\)",
      "answer": "16",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(40 - 0.88\\)",
      "answer": "978/25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 25]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{17}{88} \\div \\dfrac{3}{92}\\)",
      "answer": "391/66",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 66]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-31}{33} + \\dfrac{15}{47}\\)",
      "answer": "-962/1551",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1551]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{86}{59} \\div \\dfrac{-71}{78}\\)",
      "answer": "-6708/4189",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 4189]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0.017\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "4913/1000000000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1000000000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{4}{7} \\div 1\\)",
      "answer": "4/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 7]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{33}{31} \\div 0.029\\)",
      "answer": "33000/899",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 899]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7 + \\dfrac{49}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "105/8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 8]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.021 - \\dfrac{61}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-61063/3000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 3000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{76}{21} - \\dfrac{-23}{73}\\)",
      "answer": "6031/1533",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1533]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{59}{70} + 0.67\\)",
      "answer": "1059/700",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 700]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-48 \\div 0.12\\)",
      "answer": "-400",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{48}{97} \\div 0.045\\)",
      "answer": "3200/291",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 291]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{49}{55}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "2401/3025",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 3025]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-26 + 0.095\\)",
      "answer": "-5181/200",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 200]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{17}{18} \\div \\dfrac{27}{79}\\)",
      "answer": "1343/486",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 486]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-18}{29}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-5832/24389",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 24389]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{26}{9}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "676/81",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 81]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.092 - \\dfrac{-40}{63}\\)",
      "answer": "11449/15750",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 15750]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(\\dfrac{17}{11}\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-17/11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 11]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{11} \\div 0.045\\)",
      "answer": "200/99",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 99]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{8}{31} + 0.022\\)",
      "answer": "4341/15500",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 15500]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{30} \\div 8.6\\)",
      "answer": "7/258",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 258]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(0.85 \\leq \\dfrac{7}{23}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-4.6 - 0.1\\)",
      "answer": "-47/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 10]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-80}{51} = \\dfrac{85}{14}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-78}{17} - \\dfrac{97}{22}\\)",
      "answer": "-3365/374",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 374]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-39}{56} - 88\\)",
      "answer": "-4967/56",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 56]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-1}{31} - 3.6\\)",
      "answer": "-563/155",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 155]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.05 + \\dfrac{34}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "137/20",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 20]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-82}{37}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "6724/1369",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1369]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-86 + 1\\)",
      "answer": "-85",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{79} < \\dfrac{9}{13}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{14} \\div \\dfrac{76}{65}\\)",
      "answer": "715/1064",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1064]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{10} \\div \\dfrac{49}{18}\\)",
      "answer": "9/35",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 35]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-1.3 - 44\\)",
      "answer": "-453/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 10]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.17 + \\dfrac{33}{70}\\)",
      "answer": "449/700",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 700]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5.5 - \\dfrac{11}{35}\\)",
      "answer": "363/70",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 70]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{34}{3}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "39304/27",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 27]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(2.8 \\geq \\dfrac{13}{33}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0.093\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "8649/1000000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1000000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0.013\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "169/1000000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1000000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2 \\div \\dfrac{1}{29}\\)",
      "answer": "58",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{37}{48}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "1369/2304",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2304]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{79}{14} + \\dfrac{-53}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "-347/70",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 70]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-34}{63} + \\dfrac{83}{97}\\)",
      "answer": "1931/6111",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 6111]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{47}{49} \\div \\dfrac{-18}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "-47/126",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 126]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(-32\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-32768",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(72\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-72",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.71 + \\dfrac{57}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "6197/700",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 700]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(49\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "117649",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{86}{53} \\div -0.065\\)",
      "answer": "-17200/689",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 689]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{10} - \\dfrac{12}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "-113/70",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 70]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-53}{64} + \\dfrac{-1}{10}\\)",
      "answer": "-297/320",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 320]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{49}{38} \\div -0.2\\)",
      "answer": "-245/38",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 38]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.56 \\div \\dfrac{-65}{87}\\)",
      "answer": "-1218/1625",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1625]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(-7.5 > \\dfrac{11}{6}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{95}{9}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "857375/729",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 729]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 - 1.1\\)",
      "answer": "-11/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 10]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(4.6\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "12167/125",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 125]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.49 + \\dfrac{43}{40}\\)",
      "answer": "117/200",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 200]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-50}{57} > \\dfrac{11}{28}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(\\dfrac{35}{48}\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-35/48",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 48]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.029 \\div \\dfrac{-8}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "-261/8000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 8000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{17}{43} \\div 95\\)",
      "answer": "17/4085",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 4085]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{21}{4} - 0.46\\)",
      "answer": "479/100",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 100]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{92}{11} + \\dfrac{48}{71}\\)",
      "answer": "7060/781",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 781]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{79}{25} - \\dfrac{35}{68}\\)",
      "answer": "4497/1700",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1700]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(12 < \\dfrac{-94}{67}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{83}{59} - \\dfrac{21}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "-326/649",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 649]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{15}{34}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "3375/39304",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 39304]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-65}{99} \\div \\dfrac{-23}{16}\\)",
      "answer": "1040/2277",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2277]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(94 \\div 8.1\\)",
      "answer": "940/81",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 81]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7.8 + 38\\)",
      "answer": "229/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{55}{24}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "166375/13824",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 13824]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{17}{40}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "289/1600",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1600]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{23}{9} \\div \\dfrac{33}{26}\\)",
      "answer": "598/297",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 297]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{37}{26} \\div -0.008\\)",
      "answer": "-4625/26",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 26]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.035 + \\dfrac{47}{24}\\)",
      "answer": "299/150",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 150]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.047 \\div \\dfrac{19}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "329/19000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 19000]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{5} < \\dfrac{-5}{44}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(-47\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "2209",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{14} \\leq \\dfrac{32}{21}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-73}{75} < \\dfrac{-43}{33}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-2}{23}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-8/12167",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 12167]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{74}{21} + 0.091\\)",
      "answer": "75911/21000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 21000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{8}{37}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "64/1369",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1369]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.53 \\div \\dfrac{46}{15}\\)",
      "answer": "159/920",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 920]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3 + \\dfrac{67}{57}\\)",
      "answer": "238/57",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 57]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-1}{2} \\div \\dfrac{26}{79}\\)",
      "answer": "-79/52",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 52]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.026 + \\dfrac{35}{52}\\)",
      "answer": "1136/1625",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1625]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{23}{9} + \\dfrac{26}{31}\\)",
      "answer": "947/279",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 279]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{18} < \\dfrac{99}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(0.08 \\leq \\dfrac{-24}{29}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{55}{4} \\div 76\\)",
      "answer": "55/304",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 304]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-68}{33}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-314432/35937",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 35937]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-4.7 + \\dfrac{47}{49}\\)",
      "answer": "-1833/490",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 490]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-35}{57} \\div -11\\)",
      "answer": "35/627",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 627]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-34}{15} \\div 78\\)",
      "answer": "-17/585",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 585]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(-4.5\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "81/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 4]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(8.4 \\leq \\dfrac{11}{10}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0.5\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "1/8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 8]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-14}{3} \\div 0.71\\)",
      "answer": "-1400/213",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 213]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{62}{91} - \\dfrac{33}{10}\\)",
      "answer": "-2383/910",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 910]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{65}{47} - -0.048\\)",
      "answer": "8407/5875",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 5875]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-57}{2} \\div \\dfrac{20}{71}\\)",
      "answer": "-4047/40",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 40]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{1}{4}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "1/16",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 16]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{35}{16} + \\dfrac{75}{16}\\)",
      "answer": "55/8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 8]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-92}{15}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "8464/225",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 225]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(37 \\div \\dfrac{6}{13}\\)",
      "answer": "481/6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 6]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{3} \\div 93\\)",
      "answer": "5/279",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 279]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{21}{2}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "441/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 4]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{35}{11}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "1225/121",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 121]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(9.1\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-91/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 10]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{37}{40} + 0.09\\)",
      "answer": "203/200",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 200]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-9}{14} \\leq 30\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-75}{2} \\div 0.032\\)",
      "answer": "-9375/8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 8]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-73}{86} \\div \\dfrac{9}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "-511/774",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 774]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{22}{25} - 0.078\\)",
      "answer": "401/500",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 500]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(7.3\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "5329/100",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 100]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{3} + \\dfrac{4}{35}\\)",
      "answer": "47/105",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 105]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-2}{7} - -75\\)",
      "answer": "523/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 7]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{13}{88}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "2197/681472",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 681472]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-56}{15} \\div 76\\)",
      "answer": "-14/285",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 285]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{58}{71} \\div 0.66\\)",
      "answer": "2900/2343",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2343]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{23}{29} + \\dfrac{17}{45}\\)",
      "answer": "1528/1305",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1305]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(42 + 4.9\\)",
      "answer": "469/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 10]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0.11\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "1331/1000000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1000000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-7}{26} - 0.071\\)",
      "answer": "-4423/13000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 13000]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{91}{93} < 0.062\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(-0.4\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-8/125",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 125]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{6}{5} \\geq 63\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{10} \\div \\dfrac{-29}{62}\\)",
      "answer": "-31/145",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 145]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{47}{41} - 55\\)",
      "answer": "-2208/41",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 41]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{57}{5} - 30\\)",
      "answer": "-93/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.83 \\div \\dfrac{37}{49}\\)",
      "answer": "-4067/3700",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 3700]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{14}{3} - 0.95\\)",
      "answer": "223/60",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 60]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.02 \\div \\dfrac{38}{49}\\)",
      "answer": "49/1900",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1900]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-3.7 + 3.9\\)",
      "answer": "1/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-12}{5} + 0.037\\)",
      "answer": "-2363/1000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.095 + \\dfrac{27}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "347/100",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 100]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{23} \\div \\dfrac{70}{79}\\)",
      "answer": "79/1610",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1610]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{26}{83} \\div 77\\)",
      "answer": "26/6391",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 6391]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-61}{84} \\geq \\dfrac{-4}{55}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(8 = \\dfrac{92}{19}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{95}{59} - \\dfrac{-3}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "652/295",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 295]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(0.89 = \\dfrac{13}{72}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{38}{5} - 8.4\\)",
      "answer": "-4/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{44} + 0.6\\)",
      "answer": "157/220",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 220]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-2 + 35\\)",
      "answer": "33",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-59 - \\dfrac{93}{61}\\)",
      "answer": "-3692/61",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 61]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{44}{17} + 6.8\\)",
      "answer": "798/85",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 85]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-6.4 \\div \\dfrac{13}{45}\\)",
      "answer": "-288/13",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 13]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{58}{71} + 0\\)",
      "answer": "58/71",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 71]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{67}{70} - -35\\)",
      "answer": "2517/70",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 70]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{46}{11}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "2116/121",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 121]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{19}{36}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "361/1296",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1296]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{5} + \\dfrac{6}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "107/35",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 35]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{13}{33}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "2197/35937",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 35937]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.32 - \\dfrac{-5}{12}\\)",
      "answer": "221/300",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 300]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{12} - \\dfrac{11}{35}\\)",
      "answer": "43/420",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 420]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(\\dfrac{39}{46}\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-39/46",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 46]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.78 - -6\\)",
      "answer": "339/50",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 50]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{76}{85} + -27\\)",
      "answer": "-2219/85",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 85]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3.9 \\div -3.7\\)",
      "answer": "-39/37",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 37]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{93}{89} \\div \\dfrac{92}{81}\\)",
      "answer": "7533/8188",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 8188]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{3} \\div \\dfrac{62}{99}\\)",
      "answer": "165/62",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 62]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{94}{65} - 0.039\\)",
      "answer": "18293/13000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 13000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{10} + \\dfrac{-2}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "43/90",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 90]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1.7 \\div \\dfrac{5}{22}\\)",
      "answer": "187/25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 25]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-31}{60} + 2.5\\)",
      "answer": "119/60",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 60]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(-0.07\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "49/10000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 10000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(9.3 \\div \\dfrac{5}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "279/50",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 50]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{49}{54} \\div -0.074\\)",
      "answer": "-12250/999",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 999]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.048 - \\dfrac{12}{37}\\)",
      "answer": "-1722/4625",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 4625]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2.2 \\div 1\\)",
      "answer": "11/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 5]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(5.2 \\leq 0.048\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.058 + -9.2\\)",
      "answer": "-4571/500",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 500]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.042 + \\dfrac{5}{43}\\)",
      "answer": "3403/21500",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 21500]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{17} \\div 7.9\\)",
      "answer": "50/1343",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1343]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{31}{26} + \\dfrac{1}{44}\\)",
      "answer": "695/572",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 572]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-59}{54}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-205379/157464",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 157464]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-71 \\div \\dfrac{7}{22}\\)",
      "answer": "-1562/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 7]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0.084\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "441/62500",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 62500]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{25}{96} \\div \\dfrac{29}{14}\\)",
      "answer": "175/1392",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1392]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-77}{19} \\div \\dfrac{38}{87}\\)",
      "answer": "-6699/722",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 722]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(-0.028\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "49/62500",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 62500]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{17}{28} \\div 3.4\\)",
      "answer": "5/28",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 28]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-12}{25} \\div \\dfrac{-37}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "24/925",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 925]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(\\dfrac{5}{7}\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-5/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 7]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{69}{94}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "328509/830584",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 830584]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7.9 - \\dfrac{19}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "63/20",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 20]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(92 \\div \\dfrac{-46}{29}\\)",
      "answer": "-58",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 \\div \\dfrac{5}{59}\\)",
      "answer": "59/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{11}{12}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "121/144",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 144]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{10}{13} \\leq \\dfrac{5}{93}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-19}{28}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-6859/21952",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 21952]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{49}{47} + 0.002\\)",
      "answer": "24547/23500",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 23500]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0.037\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "1369/1000000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1000000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{42}{47}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "1764/2209",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2209]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{39}{85} \\div 0.006\\)",
      "answer": "1300/17",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 17]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{2} + 0.074\\)",
      "answer": "287/500",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 500]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{84}{61} \\div 0.092\\)",
      "answer": "21000/1403",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1403]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{17}{11} - \\dfrac{30}{17}\\)",
      "answer": "-41/187",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 187]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{56}{51} \\div \\dfrac{-7}{27}\\)",
      "answer": "-72/17",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 17]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-25}{99} \\div \\dfrac{75}{88}\\)",
      "answer": "-8/27",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 27]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(\\dfrac{33}{25}\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-33/25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 25]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.015 - \\dfrac{33}{94}\\)",
      "answer": "-3441/9400",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 9400]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{8}{9}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "64/81",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 81]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.055 + \\dfrac{-19}{33}\\)",
      "answer": "-3437/6600",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 6600]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{75}{19} < \\dfrac{52}{49}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.012 - \\dfrac{68}{13}\\)",
      "answer": "-16961/3250",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 3250]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(6.9\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-69/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 10]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{43}{82} \\div \\dfrac{-43}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "-5/82",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 82]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7 - \\dfrac{7}{20}\\)",
      "answer": "133/20",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 20]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{43}{34} < 4\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-57}{92} \\div 0.05\\)",
      "answer": "-285/23",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 23]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(26 - \\dfrac{53}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "51/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 4]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(0.94\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-47/50",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 50]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{14}{15} + \\dfrac{18}{37}\\)",
      "answer": "788/555",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 555]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(93 - \\dfrac{75}{26}\\)",
      "answer": "2343/26",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 26]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(24 - \\dfrac{18}{61}\\)",
      "answer": "1446/61",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 61]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.083 \\div \\dfrac{-35}{19}\\)",
      "answer": "-1577/35000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 35000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{13}{19} - -6.4\\)",
      "answer": "673/95",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 95]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-8}{11} \\leq 6.8\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{53}{80} - 4.3\\)",
      "answer": "-291/80",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 80]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.068 \\div -22\\)",
      "answer": "-17/5500",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 5500]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{80}{79} \\geq \\dfrac{30}{89}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(-0.015\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "3/200",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 200]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{97}{67} > \\dfrac{12}{31}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{44}{35} + -2.5\\)",
      "answer": "-87/70",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 70]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.095 \\div \\dfrac{81}{29}\\)",
      "answer": "551/16200",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 16200]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.82 + 3\\)",
      "answer": "191/50",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 50]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(\\dfrac{-2}{19}\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "2/19",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 19]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-47}{36} \\geq 0.81\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{55}{19} \\div \\dfrac{-27}{53}\\)",
      "answer": "-2915/513",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 513]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7 \\div \\dfrac{58}{97}\\)",
      "answer": "679/58",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 58]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(85 \\div -4.7\\)",
      "answer": "-850/47",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 47]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{14}{19} \\div 1.9\\)",
      "answer": "140/361",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 361]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{33}{28} \\div \\dfrac{-7}{31}\\)",
      "answer": "-1023/196",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 196]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{34}{5} - 49\\)",
      "answer": "-211/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{14}{53} - \\dfrac{15}{77}\\)",
      "answer": "283/4081",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 4081]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-1}{56}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-1/175616",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 175616]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{13}{11} + \\dfrac{5}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "81/22",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 22]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.068 - 0.069\\)",
      "answer": "-137/1000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{22}{83}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "10648/571787",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 571787]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-61}{84} + \\dfrac{3}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "1/42",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 42]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-17 - 11\\)",
      "answer": "-28",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{24}{7} - \\dfrac{43}{36}\\)",
      "answer": "563/252",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 252]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-50}{11} \\div 0.19\\)",
      "answer": "-5000/209",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 209]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{23}{72} + -34\\)",
      "answer": "-2425/72",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 72]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{98}{31} \\div \\dfrac{1}{17}\\)",
      "answer": "1666/31",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 31]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0.18\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "81/2500",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2500]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.024 \\div \\dfrac{16}{61}\\)",
      "answer": "183/2000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(6.1 - 0.07\\)",
      "answer": "603/100",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 100]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-53}{9} - 8\\)",
      "answer": "-125/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 9]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-7}{22} + \\dfrac{7}{97}\\)",
      "answer": "-525/2134",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2134]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{47}{20} + \\dfrac{9}{17}\\)",
      "answer": "979/340",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 340]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{4}{33} - \\dfrac{7}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "-215/132",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 132]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{12}{11}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "144/121",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 121]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{13}{9} \\div \\dfrac{1}{61}\\)",
      "answer": "793/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 9]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{4}{39} - \\dfrac{5}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "-179/156",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 156]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{86}{3} \\div \\dfrac{-10}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "-473/15",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 15]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(0.78 \\leq \\dfrac{77}{59}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-68}{53} - \\dfrac{53}{50}\\)",
      "answer": "-6209/2650",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2650]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0.83\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "571787/1000000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1000000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{84}{37} + \\dfrac{46}{39}\\)",
      "answer": "4978/1443",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1443]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.055 \\div \\dfrac{19}{77}\\)",
      "answer": "847/3800",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 3800]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.9 \\div \\dfrac{-18}{67}\\)",
      "answer": "-67/20",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 20]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{95}{52} < \\dfrac{41}{79}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{47} \\div \\dfrac{9}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "20/423",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 423]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{80}{27} + 0\\)",
      "answer": "80/27",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 27]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{71}{99} \\div \\dfrac{49}{94}\\)",
      "answer": "6674/4851",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 4851]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{58}{3} \\geq 0.6\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{81}{47}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "6561/2209",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2209]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{68}{11} + -0.45\\)",
      "answer": "1261/220",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 220]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{32}{27} - \\dfrac{1}{6}\\)",
      "answer": "55/54",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 54]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{10} \\div \\dfrac{38}{27}\\)",
      "answer": "27/380",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 380]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{31} \\div 58\\)",
      "answer": "1/1798",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1798]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{5} \\div 0.8\\)",
      "answer": "7/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 4]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{19} \\div \\dfrac{-99}{47}\\)",
      "answer": "-47/171",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 171]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-83}{92} - \\dfrac{-10}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "173/828",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 828]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{47} \\div -0.054\\)",
      "answer": "-5500/1269",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1269]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1.3 \\div 1\\)",
      "answer": "13/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 10]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{73}{57} \\div \\dfrac{29}{37}\\)",
      "answer": "2701/1653",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1653]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{24}{23} \\geq 5\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.044 + \\dfrac{4}{43}\\)",
      "answer": "527/10750",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 10750]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{91}{4} + \\dfrac{81}{23}\\)",
      "answer": "2417/92",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 92]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{41}{40} \\div 1\\)",
      "answer": "41/40",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 40]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4.2 + \\dfrac{7}{74}\\)",
      "answer": "1589/370",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 370]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-63}{52} \\div 0.074\\)",
      "answer": "-7875/481",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 481]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{15}{4}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "3375/64",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 64]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{46}{39} \\leq 0.68\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(1 > \\dfrac{-16}{15}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(9.6 \\div \\dfrac{54}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "88/45",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 45]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{62}{35} \\div \\dfrac{23}{26}\\)",
      "answer": "1612/805",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 805]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{56}{67} + \\dfrac{15}{14}\\)",
      "answer": "1789/938",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 938]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5.1 + \\dfrac{31}{13}\\)",
      "answer": "973/130",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 130]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{37}{49} - -3.2\\)",
      "answer": "969/245",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 245]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.86 \\div 0.23\\)",
      "answer": "86/23",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 23]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-54}{61} \\div -5.3\\)",
      "answer": "540/3233",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 3233]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4.5 + \\dfrac{2}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "31/6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 6]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{95}{44} > 3.9\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-9}{11} \\div \\dfrac{77}{95}\\)",
      "answer": "-855/847",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 847]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-23}{8} < \\dfrac{34}{83}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.062 \\div \\dfrac{-57}{91}\\)",
      "answer": "-2821/28500",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 28500]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{50} \\div -0.6\\)",
      "answer": "-1/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 10]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{68}{33} + \\dfrac{65}{42}\\)",
      "answer": "1667/462",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 462]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(-86\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-636056",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{12} < \\dfrac{-35}{83}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{88}{41}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "681472/68921",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 68921]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{49} - 0.033\\)",
      "answer": "-617/49000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 49000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 - \\dfrac{-57}{91}\\)",
      "answer": "148/91",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 91]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0.019\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "6859/1000000000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1000000000]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(-4.7 > \\dfrac{13}{74}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{93}{49}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "8649/2401",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2401]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{23}{14}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "529/196",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 196]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{23}{25} + \\dfrac{-79}{17}\\)",
      "answer": "-1584/425",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 425]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-91 \\div \\dfrac{15}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "-1001/15",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 15]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-13}{10}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-2197/1000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(6.3\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-63/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 10]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0.014\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "343/125000000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 125000000]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{36}{29} \\leq 8.2\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{46}{5} \\div \\dfrac{1}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "46",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.064 - \\dfrac{1}{16}\\)",
      "answer": "3/2000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{83}{57}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "6889/3249",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 3249]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.36 \\div \\dfrac{2}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "27/50",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 50]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{62}{11} + -4.4\\)",
      "answer": "68/55",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 55]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.095 \\div \\dfrac{-33}{53}\\)",
      "answer": "-1007/6600",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 6600]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{37}{96} \\div \\dfrac{50}{27}\\)",
      "answer": "333/1600",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1600]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{24}{29} - \\dfrac{38}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "-934/203",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 203]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(7.4 > 41\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-1 \\div 2\\)",
      "answer": "-1/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-57}{85} + \\dfrac{-59}{12}\\)",
      "answer": "-5699/1020",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1020]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-73}{9}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "5329/81",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 81]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.034 \\div 0.047\\)",
      "answer": "34/47",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 47]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{14}{27} \\div -9.2\\)",
      "answer": "-35/621",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 621]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{44}{43} \\div \\dfrac{23}{21}\\)",
      "answer": "924/989",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 989]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-9.4 \\div \\dfrac{51}{10}\\)",
      "answer": "-94/51",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 51]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{34}{7} \\div \\dfrac{-39}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "-68/273",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 273]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{25}{26} \\div \\dfrac{-75}{71}\\)",
      "answer": "-71/78",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 78]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{7} \\div -5.2\\)",
      "answer": "-55/182",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 182]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{80}{69} \\geq \\dfrac{51}{64}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-11}{43}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-1331/79507",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 79507]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{1}{5}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "1/25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 25]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{8}{39} + \\dfrac{-14}{47}\\)",
      "answer": "-170/1833",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1833]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{31}{53}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "961/2809",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2809]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{87}{25} - \\dfrac{87}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "-1827/100",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 100]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-7.9 - \\dfrac{36}{13}\\)",
      "answer": "-1387/130",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 130]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{28}{43} > \\dfrac{11}{10}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{57}{62} - \\dfrac{49}{79}\\)",
      "answer": "1465/4898",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 4898]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-19}{5} \\div \\dfrac{38}{47}\\)",
      "answer": "-47/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 10]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{9}{10}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "729/1000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-14}{73} - \\dfrac{-35}{53}\\)",
      "answer": "1813/3869",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 3869]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{29}{93} - \\dfrac{97}{55}\\)",
      "answer": "-7426/5115",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 5115]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-29}{52}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "841/2704",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2704]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-72}{91} \\div \\dfrac{61}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "-72/793",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 793]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.28 - \\dfrac{-26}{29}\\)",
      "answer": "447/725",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 725]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{9}{68} \\div 4.9\\)",
      "answer": "45/1666",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1666]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-6.3 \\div \\dfrac{25}{83}\\)",
      "answer": "-5229/250",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 250]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.058 \\div \\dfrac{91}{51}\\)",
      "answer": "1479/45500",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 45500]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{43}{27}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "1849/729",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 729]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{47}{80} - \\dfrac{65}{89}\\)",
      "answer": "-1017/7120",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 7120]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.009 \\div \\dfrac{20}{41}\\)",
      "answer": "369/20000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 20000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{1}{9}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "1/729",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 729]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{18}{19} + \\dfrac{-7}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "29/171",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 171]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{4}{55} \\div \\dfrac{1}{37}\\)",
      "answer": "148/55",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 55]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.048 - \\dfrac{61}{81}\\)",
      "answer": "-7139/10125",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 10125]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{47}{92} + -3.2\\)",
      "answer": "-1237/460",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 460]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{45}{28} \\div \\dfrac{21}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "75/196",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 196]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{29}{21} - \\dfrac{34}{77}\\)",
      "answer": "31/33",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 33]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3 + 85\\)",
      "answer": "88",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{10} - 0.8\\)",
      "answer": "-1/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{28}{19}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "21952/6859",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 6859]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.004 + \\dfrac{17}{20}\\)",
      "answer": "427/500",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 500]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-21}{31} + \\dfrac{56}{89}\\)",
      "answer": "-133/2759",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2759]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(22 > 28\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{41}{17} \\div \\dfrac{77}{53}\\)",
      "answer": "2173/1309",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1309]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-3.4 \\div \\dfrac{36}{23}\\)",
      "answer": "-391/180",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 180]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(22 + \\dfrac{74}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "140/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 3]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0.011\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "1331/1000000000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1000000000]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(0.24 > 8\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(97 + \\dfrac{7}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "880/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 9]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5.4 - \\dfrac{13}{16}\\)",
      "answer": "367/80",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 80]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-17}{15} \\div 0.15\\)",
      "answer": "-68/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 9]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.5 \\div \\dfrac{82}{89}\\)",
      "answer": "89/164",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 164]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{21}{16} + \\dfrac{-2}{95}\\)",
      "answer": "1963/1520",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1520]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(0.45\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-9/20",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 20]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.085 \\div \\dfrac{35}{47}\\)",
      "answer": "-799/7000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 7000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(42\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "1764",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{72}{65} \\leq \\dfrac{61}{19}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(6 - 23\\)",
      "answer": "-17",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5 \\div \\dfrac{5}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{90}{37} + 4\\)",
      "answer": "238/37",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 37]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{41}{86}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "68921/636056",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 636056]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.23 \\div \\dfrac{-20}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "-207/2000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2000]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{58}{63} > \\dfrac{89}{61}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(24\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "13824",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{46}{47} \\div \\dfrac{43}{6}\\)",
      "answer": "276/2021",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2021]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{42}{23} + 7.8\\)",
      "answer": "1107/115",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 115]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(20\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-20",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.78 \\div \\dfrac{-25}{24}\\)",
      "answer": "-468/625",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 625]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{95}{29} - \\dfrac{58}{75}\\)",
      "answer": "5443/2175",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2175]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{50}{19} \\div \\dfrac{13}{73}\\)",
      "answer": "3650/247",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 247]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-1.2 - 27\\)",
      "answer": "-141/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 5]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{81}{26} + \\dfrac{29}{85}\\)",
      "answer": "7639/2210",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2210]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{37}{24} + \\dfrac{83}{25}\\)",
      "answer": "2917/600",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 600]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(0.044 \\geq \\dfrac{4}{99}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-47}{57} + \\dfrac{-47}{22}\\)",
      "answer": "-3713/1254",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1254]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.027 \\div \\dfrac{83}{65}\\)",
      "answer": "351/16600",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 16600]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{99}{82}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "9801/6724",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 6724]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{27}{37} \\div 0.02\\)",
      "answer": "1350/37",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 37]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{23}{31}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "12167/29791",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 29791]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.044 - 0.89\\)",
      "answer": "-423/500",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 500]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(-4\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "16",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{86}{47} \\div \\dfrac{9}{29}\\)",
      "answer": "2494/423",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 423]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(8.9 > -0.01\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 + -19\\)",
      "answer": "-19",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{68}{91} \\div \\dfrac{47}{65}\\)",
      "answer": "340/329",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 329]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{17}{18} \\div 66\\)",
      "answer": "17/1188",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1188]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-9}{94} \\div 8.3\\)",
      "answer": "-45/3901",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 3901]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{11} - \\dfrac{-43}{72}\\)",
      "answer": "977/792",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 792]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{10}{3} - \\dfrac{1}{13}\\)",
      "answer": "127/39",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 39]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{16}{21}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "256/441",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 441]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.001 + \\dfrac{23}{85}\\)",
      "answer": "4583/17000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 17000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(-8.2\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "1681/25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 25]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{12}{61} - \\dfrac{5}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "-281/122",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 122]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(0.038 \\geq 5.2\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-23}{14}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-12167/2744",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2744]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(\\dfrac{-3}{10}\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "3/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 10]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{97}{51} - \\dfrac{-71}{99}\\)",
      "answer": "4408/1683",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1683]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(-0.79\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "6241/10000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 10000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{9}{14} + \\dfrac{-7}{43}\\)",
      "answer": "289/602",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 602]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(-0.94 \\geq \\dfrac{5}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{27}{13} \\div \\dfrac{3}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "72/13",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 13]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-1}{19} - \\dfrac{-79}{96}\\)",
      "answer": "1405/1824",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1824]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{36}{43} < -2\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{4} < \\dfrac{57}{10}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8 + -93\\)",
      "answer": "-85",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(-27\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-19683",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-48}{19} + \\dfrac{60}{97}\\)",
      "answer": "-3516/1843",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1843]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{38}{23} \\div -0.057\\)",
      "answer": "-2000/69",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 69]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3 \\div -0.97\\)",
      "answer": "-300/97",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 97]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.019 - \\dfrac{33}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "-8231/1000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.6 \\div 0.045\\)",
      "answer": "40/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 3]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(4.5 < -0.23\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{17}{16} \\geq \\dfrac{77}{40}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-1}{65} \\leq \\dfrac{-10}{17}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{67}{27} - \\dfrac{77}{89}\\)",
      "answer": "3884/2403",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2403]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.057 - \\dfrac{-64}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "64627/11000",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 11000]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(6.8 \\div 0.6\\)",
      "answer": "34/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 3]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{55}{4} + -0.036\\)",
      "answer": "6857/500",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 500]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.11 + 0.19\\)",
      "answer": "3/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 10]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{20}{47} \\div \\dfrac{79}{27}\\)",
      "answer": "540/3713",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 3713]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{10}{33} > \\dfrac{19}{16}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.61 - \\dfrac{56}{85}\\)",
      "answer": "-83/1700",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 1700]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{83}{49} \\geq \\dfrac{37}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{19}{10} \\div \\dfrac{31}{28}\\)",
      "answer": "266/155",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 155]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(\\dfrac{-1}{2}\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "1/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 2]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5.5 + \\dfrac{37}{30}\\)",
      "answer": "101/15",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 15]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{98}{19}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "941192/6859",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 6859]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{63}{13} \\div \\dfrac{46}{91}\\)",
      "answer": "441/46",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 46]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{39}{50} \\div \\dfrac{51}{29}\\)",
      "answer": "377/850",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 850]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.015 - -74\\)",
      "answer": "14803/200",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec", "mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 200]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{77}{61} \\div \\dfrac{98}{75}\\)",
      "answer": "825/854",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 854]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-1}{6} - \\dfrac{30}{97}\\)",
      "answer": "-277/582",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 582]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{85}{53}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "614125/148877",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr", "mix", "dec"],
      "expectedDenominators": [0, 148877]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{71} > \\dfrac{1}{80}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": ["True", "False"]
    }
  ]
}
